

# Gagandeep KN

IT, 5th sem, National Institute Of Technology, Karnataka

In my two years at NITK college, I've completed a great deal of coursework and best practices including programming languages such as C/C++, Java, Python, HTML, JS etc where I learned and applied skills in 6 of the mini projects. In addition, I spent the past term of my time with clubs like photography and media that covers all the events at the college and been playing for NITK cricket team apart from the coursework from the college, i have completed certified courses related to Machine Learning. I believe I would make an excellent addition to your team. This would help me grow my realworld experience in the technology industry and help me further develop and refine my application

gagandeepkn.181it215@nitk.edu.in

+91 9986655357



580007, Dharwad

#### **EDUCATION**

# Information Technology 5th Sem

National Institute Of Technology, Karnataka

2018 - Present

Current CGPA: 7.14

Courses

- Data structure and algorithm
- operating Systems
- Database management system
- web technology and application
- Computer networking

# **Pre-university** Expert PU College

2016 - 2018

Courses

- physics
- chemistry

Graduated with 94.25% in PCMC

- mathematics
- computer science

# High school St. John's CBSE School

2013 - 2016

achievements

- Elected to President for Student council in 2014-15 Graduated with 10 CGPA

- Capitan of school cricket team for inter-school matches

## **PROJECTS**

#### Machine learning

- Deep Neural Network for Image Classification: Application
- Planar data classification with one hidden layer
- Convolutional Model: application
- Trigger word detection
- Character level language model Dinosaurus land

#### Data-Structure and Algorithm

- Bulls and cows: Game
- Snake Route: Game using different search algorithms and Al

#### Web Technology and Applications

- Cycle-On: Bicycle renting system

#### Other Projects

- File system using Trie DS
- Remote system monitor: Computer networking

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Database Management	• • • • •
Python	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Machine learning	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
C/C++	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Android studio/X-code	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$
Vantiq/VAIL	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Web development	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Java	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$ $\circ$
Photography	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Alphamarc (06/2020 – Present)

Worked as intern at www.alphamarc.com consulting with www.storeintelligence.com as developer to implement cloud based solution for their IoT Electronic Shelf Label products. Store Intelligence was moving from their JBOSS and PostGRES database based monolithic server solution for their ESL product to Cloud based solution using Vantig Platform. I was involved in developing internal debug utilities that involved communication between ESLS and Access Points. The communication was based on proprietary RF 2.4 GHz protocol. I worked on Java, Javascript, Vantiq Platform's proprietary programming language named VAIL.

#### Orsus Consulting Services (07/2020 - 08/2020)

Worked as intern at Orsus Consulting Services as web developer to build a website for the company. I was involved in developent of homepage and other pages using: HTML,CSS,JavaScript

## **CERTIFICATES**

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

Structuring Machine Learning Projects

Convolutional Neural Networks

Sequence Models